

Nikiforos Karamitros

Full Stack Developer



Experience

Junior Full Stack Dev Jul 2023 - Present

Chemical Safety Software

Sales Representative Aug 2022 - Jan 2023

Plaisio Computers, Peristeri GR

Education

Oct 2021 - Jun 2023 Software Engineer

IEK AKMI, Athens GR

Web Designer / Game Developer Oct 2021 - Oct 2022

IEK AKMI, Athens GR

Certificates

The Complete SQL Cource 2024 - SQL Apr 2024

Server

Udemy

Game Design 101 - 301 Mar 2023

IEK AKMI

Jan 2023 **Arduino Programming And App**

Development

IEK AKMI

PC Troubleshooting And Repair Jan 2023

IEK AKMI

About Me

I am a passionate Full Stack Developer, with a strong background in a similar position in which I honed mostly my .NET skills, as well as expanded and refined my SQL & Database Design knowledge. I have worked on languages and tools such as Python, Java and Unity through my personal projects

Being a Technology based Sales Representative at Plaisio Computers, as well as having a huge interest in keeping up with new technologies, I have both a broad and deep understanding of hardware in the PC and Networking space.

My biggest ambition is learning and understanding as much as I possibly can with every aspect of technology, whether it's hardware, software and everything in-between.

Personal details

Website nickkay.com

Github:

github.com/NickKay0

Skills

MSSQL / MYSQL / SQL

.NET Development (C,C#,C++)

Unity Game Engine

Excel / Word / Powerpoint

HTML / CSS / JS

Python

Java

Languages

Greek

English

Hobbies

- Programming, Coding And App Development
- Playing & Developing Games

- Digital And Pixel Art
- PC Building And Upgrading